The URL that we built looks good, and the JSON string from the server,
我们构建的URL看起来很好，并且从服务器返回的JSON数据也看起来不错，
also looks good, however, it still is one long string.
但是，这仍然是一个长字符串。
Let's look at it more carefully to see what data, we should extract from it.
让我们再更加仔细的看这是什么数据，我们应该取出他。
In order to make sense of the string that comes back from the server.
为了能够理解从服务器返回的字符串。
We can put it through a JSON formatter or a JSON prettifier.
我们能够将他传入 JSON Formatter 或者 JSON prettifier。
If you Google for
如果你 Google 这些
those terms, you'll be able to find a helpful tool, such as this one.
词，你能找到很有帮助的工具，比如这个。
Here we pasted the result of the web query.
这里我们黏贴web查询的结果。
Then it formatted the output for us, showing us the hierarchy of these element.
然后他为我们构建了输出，显示了这些元素的层级关系。
Now based on the wire frames that you saw for the sunshine app,
现在基于在 sunshine app 的框图，
can you tell us which of these leaf nodes we care about extracting?
你能不能告诉我哪些叶子节点我们想抽离他？
Even though we will have to traverse through parent nodes, for the purposes of
尽管我们将不能不遍历这些父节点，为了
the quiz on the next screen, we're just looking at the leaf nodes.
下个测验，我们只是看看叶子节点。
Make your selection below on which attributes we'll need to
在下面做出选择，哪些属性你将要
display the list of forecasts.
显示在天气预报列表里。